

 \searrow

atiikmahmud@gmail.com



+8801749941982



Dhaka, Bangladesh



atiikmahmud.github.io/portfolio/



linkedin.com/in/atiikmahmud



github.com/atiikmahmud

SKILLS

C/C++

HTML



Bootsrap

JavaScript

React

PHP

Laravel

WordPress

MySQL

LANGUAGES

Bengali

Native or Bilingual Proficiency

English

Professional Working Proficiency

INTERESTS

Web Design

Web Development

Database

Atik Mahmud

Junior Software Engineer

I am an Experienced Software Engineer. Skilled in web development and have more then few years of working experience. I have strong knowledge and working experience in front-end, back-end and database technologies. I am interested in working in using new technology. I enjoy being part of a team, teaching and learning new things from my teammate.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Junior Software Engineer Shajgoj Limited

02/2022 - Present Dhaka, Bangladesh

Bangladesh's number one beauty & personal care e-commerce is SHAJGOJ.

Responsibility

As a web developer, I have to work both front-end and back-end team. I also have to work with the project manager and senior developers to work with the requirement of the project.

Junior Software Engineer IOTMDCP Industries Limited

08/2020 - 01/2022

IT Company in Rajshahi.

Responsibility

I have to work both front-end and back-end team. I have to submit my assigned task in time to the senior developer. I have to attend daily scram meeting between developers and project manager.

ORGANIZATIONS

Satt Academy, Rajshahi (06/2018 - 01/2020)

I learned to the web application at SATT Academy, here I learned website design and development and then worked as a trainer.

PROJECTS

E-commerce Website at Shajgoj Limited (02/2022 - Present)

As a web developer, I have to work at back-end team. I also have to work with the project manager and senior developers to work with the requirement of the project by Laravel Framework of PHP.

E-commerce Website for Star International

- E-commerce website by WordPress CMS of PHP.
- http://starinternational.xyz

Portfolio Website for Star International

- Static Portfolio website.
- http://starintbd.com

E-commerce Website for Dreamland Technologies

- E-commerce website by Core PHP
- http://mall.dreamlandtechbd.com

EDUCATION

B. Sc in Computer Science and EngineeringVarendra University

01/2016 - 01/2020

Rajshahi, Bangladesh

Rajshahi, Bangladesh

HSC (Science)Varendra College

2015 Rajshahi, Bangladesh